Inflection AI is a private company,
is a private artificial intelligence company,
based in the United States,
and it has a product that we're gonna be talking about
in this very lecture.
So the product itself doesn't seem to have a Wikipedia page,
but the company does.
So as you see, it says Inflection AI Inc
is an American technology company,
which has developed machine learning
and generative artificial intelligence hardware and apps,
founded in 2022, right?
And yes, it's a private company as you see.
The company is structured as a public benefit corporation,
and it's headquarters headquartered in Palo Alto.
Yep, California.
And this is what we have about the company,